Lish mss., 1951-2017 LMC 2404
Lilly Library
- II. Writings
  - By Other Authors
    - Rooke (end) - Schutt, Christine (Box 73)
      - Sarki, Michael T. (Box 73)
        - Zimble Zamble Zumble (Box 73)
          - For Bricking Raleigh Tavern (Box 73)
          - Rubble, and the Lammikin (Box 73)
          - In My Difficulties with Direction (Box 73)
          - Untimely Is this Nomad (Box 73)
          - On the Destruction of a Sentiment (Box 73)
          - Biscuits and Striola (Box 73)
          - Am I Still Holding Here? (Box 73)
          - Gnomon's Bois de Rose (Box 73)
          - When Vincent Paid His Rent (Box 73)
          - Of Chippage and the Bud (Box 73)
          - A Winsome Jest and Behold the Giver (Box 73)
          - Rarities in Descending Orders (Box 73)
          - A Modern Architecture (Box 73)
          - Saint-Rémy (Box 73)
          - In Her Garden Coat and Dungarees (Box 73)
          - New York's Ninety-Sixth and Teacher (Box 73)
          - Flaming on the Banks of Ohio (Box 73)
          - Will the Person on This Bus Please Move Over? (Box 73)
          - And Only If Her Insult Was My Name (Box 73)
          - Gregori's Theater of Belief (Box 73)
          - Night in the Sidewalk Café (Box 73)
          - And Will You Haul Away This Marvel? (Box 73)
          - A Leg Off Every Wishbone (Box 73)
          - The Cornhuskers Gather (Box 73)
          - The Immovable Steel of Donegal (Box 73)
          - Effacing the Clown (Box 73)
          - Tweezers and Gauze, Unguents That Percolate (Box 73)
          - Periods Before the Aggressive Banking (Box 73)
          - Sitting on the Arm of Robert's Mouth (Box 73)
          - Under the Bellows (Box 73)
          - Borrowed from Death Row (Box 73)
          - Unabashed (Box 73)
          - Could Be Astigmia, or a Phantasmagoria (Box 73)
          - Dialing for Dharma (Box 73)
          - Driving Gretchen's Doll (Box 73)
          - Missouri, Das Unheimliche (Box 73)
      - Sayer (Box 73)
        - Property Withheld (Box 73)
      - Sayer, Allison (Box 73)
        - [I am stone sober. My neighbor is dying…] (Box 73)
      - Scherer, Catherine (Box 73)
        - The Education of Henri Mattisse Withheld [aka The Learning of Henri Matisse] (Box 73)
      - Scherer, Steven H. (Box 73)
        - Writings (Box 73)
          - Plot and Character Summary of Countdown to Survival (Box 73)
          - Plot and Character Summary of Slow Pan of Earth in Flame (Box 73)
          - What the Cameras Saw (Box 73)
        - Countdown to Survival Draft 1 (Box 73)
        - Countdown to Survival Draft 2, (2 folders) (Box 73)
        - Slow Pan of Earth in Flame (Box 73)
      - Schmidt, Dorey (Box 73)
        - riverSedge (Box 73)
      - Schumacher, James (Box 73)
        - Grenade (Box 73)
      - Schutt, Christine, (3 folders) (Box 73)
        - Stories, (2 folders) (Box 73)
          - Because I Could Not Stop for Death (Box 73)
          - Do I Know You? (Box 73)
          - Erigeron azures, Drkest of All (Box 73)
          - Every Time We Say Good-bye (Box 73)
          - I Am Reading Jane Eyre Again (Box 73)
          - Metropolis [aka In the Country of Ease] (Box 73)
          - [Our Nana, in the world before the automobile…] (Box 73)
          - Religion (Box 73)
          - So Many Short Sudden Motions (Box 73)
          - Stephen, Michael, Patrick, John (Box 73)
          - [There is a man on top of her…] (Box 73)
        - The Dependence (Box 73)
    - Schutt, Geoff - Sparks (Box 74)
      - Schutt, Geoff (Box 74)
        - The Ball [aka What We've Learned from Roger Maris] (Box 74)
        - Hygiene [aka The Monsters] (Box 74)
      - Schwartz, Jason (Box 74)
        - Antwerp (Box 74)
        - Dead Bark (Box 74)
        - Feet in the Mud in the Sun (Box 74)
        - Hooks in the Wall (Box 74)
        - Ox (Box 74)
        - Ram (Box 74)
        - Ram Farm (Box 74)
        - Rope Tail (Box 74)
        - The Staves (Box 74)
        - The Women in the Window (Box 74)
      - Scroogins, Daryl (Box 74)
        - Delphic (Box 74)
        - A Few Small Adjustments (Box 74)
        - The Hounding (Box 74)
        - Levels of Contentment (Box 74)
      - Shapiro, Harvey (Box 74)
        - A Day's Portion (Box 74)
          - These Are the Streets (Box 74)
          - Celebrations (Box 74)
          - Questions (Box 74)
          - New York Summer (Box 74)
          - Meditation on a Brooklyn Bench (Box 74)
          - City Ethic (Box 74)
          - New York Note (Box 74)
          - Hollywood Note (Box 74)
          - Brooklyn Heights (Box 74)
          - Brooklyn Nights (Box 74)
          - Fact (Box 74)
          - Monday in New York (Box 74)
          - Lessons (Box 74)
          - August, from Brooklyn (Box 74)
          - Lower East Side (Box 74)
          - Lit-Crit (Box 74)
          - Different Schools (Box 74)
          - On Writing (Box 74)
          - Sunday School (Box 74)
          - Bible Lesson (Box 74)
          - Genesis (Box 74)
          - After the Fall (Box 74)
          - For Paul Celan and Primo Levi (Box 74)
          - Tonight (Box 74)
          - Loyalty (Box 74)
          - Snapshot (Box 74)
          - Assimilation (Box 74)
          - Natural History (Box 74)
          - Jerusalem (Box 74)
          - Bronx Elegy (Box 74)
          - A Tel Aviv Notebook (Box 74)
          - Aubade (Box 74)
          - His Age (Box 74)
          - Table Scene (Box 74)
          - History (Box 74)
          - The Encounter (Box 74)
          - Politics (Box 74)
          - Pleasure (Box 74)
          - Belief Systems (Box 74)
          - Another Story (Box 74)
          - Masha (Box 74)
          - Education (Box 74)
          - A Story (Box 74)
          - Fancy (Box 74)
          - How It Ended (Box 74)
          - When the Spirit (Box 74)
          - Before Sleep (Box 74)
          - On My Portrait by a Rose Garden (Box 74)
          - Ocean Dawn (Box 74)
          - The Text (Box 74)
          - For Charles Reznikoff (Box 74)
          - Saroyan (Box 74)
          - Portrait (Box 74)
          - Losses (Box 74)
          - Goodbye, Rio (Box 74)
          - Family Man (Box 74)
          - A Day (Box 74)
          - Tranquility (Box 74)
          - 1943 (Box 74)
          - Blowing Smoke (Box 74)
          - Iggy (Box 74)
          - Vineyard Autumn (Box 74)
          - Sunday (Box 74)
          - Selfportrait (Box 74)
          - The Boast (Box 74)
          - Years Ago (Box 74)
          - Shoppers (Box 74)
          - A Day's Portion (Box 74)
      - Shaukat, A. (Box 74)
        - Mourning (Box 74)
        - West of Amarillo (Box 74)
      - Shaw, Dave (Box 74)
        - Her Book (Box 74)
        - A Man's Hands (Box 74)
      - Shawver, James E. (Box 74)
        - James E. Shawver to Q (Box 74)
      - Sherwood, Kay E. (Box 74)
        - Clothes (or For Gordon) (Box 74)
      - Sefaris, George (Box 74)
        - Mythistorema (Box 74)
      - Seiler, Barry (Box 74)
        - The Lake (Box 74)
        - Namesake (Box 74)
      - Seiter, Dave (Box 74)
        - Breakfast (Box 74)
        - Things You Should Know (Box 74)
      - Selby, Jr., Hubert (Box 74)
        - The Roon (Box 74)
      - Selzer, Richard, (4 folders) (Box 74)
        - Stories, (2 folders) (Box 74)
          - Abortion (Box 74)
          - Bald, or Rheum at the Top [aka Bald! and Balderdash ] (Box 74)
          - Belly (Box 74)
          - Chaucer's Tale (Box 74)
          - Five Appointments with the Discuss Thrower (Box 74)
          - Good Manners in the O.R. (Box 74)
          - The Harbinger (Box 74)
          - In Praise of Smoking (Box 74)
          - The Knife (Box 74)
          - The Laugh [aka On Laughter] (Box 74)
          - On Birdwatching (Box 74)
          - Pages from a Wound Dresser's Diary (Box 74)
          - Skin (Box 74)
          - The Stone (Box 74)
          - Tales (Box 74)
        - Belly (Box 74)
        - The Corpse [aka Death] (Box 74)
      - Severy, Bruce (Box 74)
        - Diary of a Love Survivor [aka Diary of a Citizen] (Box 74)
      - Shablan, D.L. (Box 74)
        - A Lesson in Blood (Box 74)
      - Sharma, Akhil (Box 74)
        - The Blue Umbrella Man (Box 74)
      - Sharpe, Matthew (Box 74)
        - Goldilocks (Box 74)
      - Shawver, James E. (Box 74)
        - Buttermilk (Box 74)
      - Shelnutt, Eve (Box 74)
        - Feet (Box 74)
      - Sherman, Martin (Box 74)
        - The Evening News [aka You Are There: Armenie 1988] (Box 74)
        - The Sliver [aka Slivers] (Box 74)
        - The Story [aka Faith] (Box 74)
        - Thinking (Box 74)
      - Shetzline (Box 74)
        - Property [aka The Compleat Angler] (Box 74)
      - Shields, David (Box 74)
        - The Gun in the Grass at Your Feet (Box 74)
      - Shields, James (Box 74)
        - I See [aka the AnaMuong Railway] (Box 74)
      - Siegel, Helen D. (Box 74)
        - An Unstory (Box 74)
      - Siegel, Marc (Box 74)
        - The Assistant [aka Making Fire] (Box 74)
        - The Fixer (Box 74)
        - Gaz (Box 74)
        - Housecall (Box 74)
        - Life Not of Kierkegard [aka Orphaned] (Box 74)
        - Not Some Other Game (Box 74)
      - Siegel, Sally Dewald (Box 74)
        - Forty Reasons for Segregation (Box 74)
      - Signor, Randy Michael (Box 74)
        - He Said, I Am a Hero (Box 74)
      - Simon, Kelly (Box 74)
        - Kelly Simon to Q [aka I Know Who This Is] (Box 74)
        - Seligman's Hat [aka Kaliakin's Hat] (Box 74)
      - Singleton, George (Box 74)
        - George Singleton to Q (Box 74)
      - Smith, Lee (Box 74)
        - The Seven Deadly Sins (Box 74)
      - Smith, Richard D. (Box 74)
        - Einstein, the Movies (Box 74)
      - Smock, Frederick (Box 74)
        - Federick Smock to Q (Box 74)
      - Smoodin, Roberta, (3 folders) (Box 74)
        - Ursus Major, (2 folders) (Box 74)
        - [Joseph, who's called the King…] (Box 74)
      - Snee, Pat (Box 74)
        - Sex Habits of Suburban Couples (Box 74)
      - Solomon, Gregory (Box 74)
        - Glitter (Box 74)
      - Sorkin, Ken (Box 74)
        - Twenty % Tippers Newsletters (Box 74)
      - Sorrells, Helen (Box 74)
        - Town I Left (Box 74)
      - Sorrentino, Gilbert (Box 74)
        - Decades [aka The Sick and the Wounded] (Box 74)
        - In Loveland (Box 74)
      - Spackman, W.M. (Box 74)
        - An Armful of Warn Girl (Box 74)
      - Spain, Chris (Box 74)
        - Entrepeneurs [aka Right Stuff Gone Wrong] (Box 74)
      - Spanbauer, Tom, (2 folders) (Box 74)
        - Stories (Box 74)
          - Idiot Boy (Box 74)
          - Like Sea Animals [aka Where the Owls Chase the Chickens] (Box 74)
        - Faraway Places (Box 74)
      - Spark, Muriel (Box 74)
        - Crisis in New York (Box 74)
      - Sparks, Rennie (Box 74)
        - Dirtbags (Box 74)
    - Sparling - Sudnow (Box 75)
      - Sparling, Ken, (4 folders) (Box 75)
        - Stories and Poems (Box 75)
          - Book Review (Box 75)
          - Currency (Box 75)
          - Dot Matrix Meets the Melancholy Baby [aka What I Really Want to Give Her] (Box 75)
          - I Am One of the Caretakers Here (Box 75)
          - It's All Coming Back to Me Now (Box 75)
          - I've Been Thinking, Dad (Box 75)
          - Job (Box 75)
          - Judgement (Box 75)
          - Mozambique In One Place I Know I'll Never See (Box 75)
          - Note (Box 75)
          - Pick It (Box 75)
          - Thank God (Box 75)
          - Then One Day (Box 75)
          - Tom (Box 75)
          - The Trouble with Lish (Box 75)
          - Turning Point, or Moment of Crisis (Box 75)
          - Yes, Yes…But What Do You Do When It's Raining [aka Get There Now, I Don't Have a Lot of Time ] (Box 75)
        - Dad Says He Saw You at the Mall (Box 75)
        - The Poetling Speaks (Box 75)
        - Terror (Box 75)
          - Terror (Box 75)
          - Compass Things (Box 75)
          - Limits (Box 75)
          - Garbage (Box 75)
          - Old Man in a Webbed Chair (Box 75)
          - Mould (Box 75)
          - Intercourse (Box 75)
          - Tragedy (Box 75)
          - Sex (Box 75)
          - Light (Box 75)
          - Fido (Box 75)
          - Mumbley (Box 75)
          - People Who Died: Supplement to the 1993 Edition (includes index) (Box 75)
          - Discomfort (Box 75)
          - Sick (Box 75)
          - You Want Bag? (Box 75)
          - Tom (Box 75)
          - Bob Rode the Train (Box 75)
          - The Bread of Life (Box 75)
          - Hey, Look at Me, the Dickhead! (Box 75)
          - Just Another Shadow on My Lawn (Box 75)
          - Alone (Box 75)
          - Stuff You See Everyday (Box 75)
          - The Sun Was Shining (Box 75)
          - Then (Box 75)
          - Hot Dogs (Box 75)
          - Can't Say (Box 75)
          - Persephone (Box 75)
          - Smell (Box 75)
          - Decorating Stories (Box 75)
          - Tricks (Box 75)
          - Scheduling (Box 75)
          - Added Bonus: Great Tits (Box 75)
          - A Lot of It (Box 75)
          - Sorry (Box 75)
          - Tutti's Story (Box 75)
          - Legend (Box 75)
          - Hey Gwen (Box 75)
          - Frail (Box 75)
          - In the Bud (Box 75)
          - The Black Rod Club (Box 75)
      - Spencer, Darrell (Box 75)
        - Hops (Box 75)
        - Loose in the Mail (Box 75)
      - Spencer, Scott (Box 75)
        - The Tip [aka Hope] (Box 75)
        - Wrong Number (Box 75)
      - Staley, Kathryn (Box 75)
        - Fish Tale (Box 75)
        - Petey Capete (Box 75)
      - Stanton, Maura (Box 75)
        - The Poetry of Raymond Carver's Stories (Box 75)
      - Stein, Marion (Box 75)
        - Pogo (Box 75)
      - Stein, Scott (Box 75)
        - The Stacker (Box 75)
      - Steinberg, Susan (Box 75)
        - Isla (Box 75)
        - Standstill (Box 75)
        - There's a Window (Box 75)
      - Steinem, Gloria (Box 75)
        - Digging Shirley (Box 75)
      - Steiner, Robert (Box 75)
        - The Rose Man's Tale (Box 75)
      - Stern, Steve (Box 75)
        - Stories (Box 75)
          - Aaron Makes a Match (Box 75)
          - The Book of Mordecai (Box 75)
          - Bruno's Metamorphosis (Box 75)
          - Goldfinch & Son (Box 75)
          - Isaac and the Undertaker's Daughter (Box 75)
          - Rudolph Finkl's Apprenticeship (Box 75)
          - A Sentimental Journey (Box 75)
        - Harry Kaplan's Adventures Underground (Box 75)
      - Stevens, Brooke (Box 75)
        - Hitch-hiking [aka Sleep Well] (Box 75)
        - Minnows (Box 75)
      - St. Germain, Richard (Box 75)
        - The Bomber [aka School] (Box 75)
        - [He wants to change the storm-door window…] (Box 75)
        - It Wasn't Thanksgiving [aka Leftover] (Box 75)
        - The Last Trash Day (Box 75)
        - My Name Is Richard [aka Enough] (Box 75)
        - Not Home (Box 75)
        - Some Shoes (Box 75)
        - Untitled Fiction in Progress (Box 75)
        - Workout (Box 75)
      - Stickney, John (Box 75)
        - Six Characters in Search of an Author (Box 75)
      - Stone, Alan (Box 75)
        - The Hobbyist and the Communists (Box 75)
      - Stone, Alma (Box 75)
        - I'm Waving Tomorrow (Box 75)
        - The Rope Rock Singer [aka The Traveller] (Box 75)
        - Viva La Tva (Box 75)
      - Stone, Lee (Box 75)
        - Their Sizes Run Differently (Box 75)
      - Stone, Robert (Box 75)
        - The Last Good Run (Box 75)
      - Stone, Sandra (Box 75)
        - Salmon [aka Paybeck] (Box 75)
      - Street, Steve (Box 75)
        - Welcome (Box 75)
      - Strozier, Robert M. (Box 75)
        - Sir (Box 75)
      - Styron, William (Box 75)
        - The Way of the Warrior (Box 75)
      - Sudnow, David, (8 folders) (Box 76)
        - Making Sense of Sights: The Social Organization of Looking (Box 76)
        - Between Two Keyboards [would later become From Here to There then Talk's Body] (Box 76)
        - From Here to There Draft 1 [would later become Talk's Body] (Box 76)
        - From Here to There Draft 2 (Box 76)
        - From Here to There Galleys (Box 76)
        - Talk's Body Proof (Box 76)
        - Talk's Body Printer's ms (Box 76)
        - Talk's Body Master Proof (Box 76)
    - Sudnow (end) - Thomas, James (Box 76)
      - Sudnow, David (end), (5 folders) (Box 76)
        - Talk's Body Master Proof 2 (Box 76)
        - Talk's Body Blues (Box 76)
        - Talk's Body Pages (Box 76)
        - Talk's Body Repros (Box 76)
      - Sulaitis, D. Sabina (Box 76)
        - Out the Window [aka Cowboy on Columbus] (Box 76)
      - Sullins, Wayne (Box 76)
        - A Little Something (Box 76)
        - The Mother in the Booth (Box 76)
        - This Time (Box 76)
      - Sullivan, Julie (Box 76)
        - [I was sitting on a crate in the sunshine…] (Box 76)
        - [I went to visit Dawson at the office…] (Box 76)
      - Susswein, Charles (Box 76)
        - The Dinner [aka I Could Have Eaten a Horse] (Box 76)
      - Svoboda, Therese (Box 76)
        - I Dreamt He Fell Three Floors and Lived (Box 76)
        - La Historia Is a Woman (Box 76)
        - Trailer (Box 76)
        - Sweet, Floyd Sonny (Box 76)
        - An Introduction to the Complete Works of Clifford Irving (Box 76)
      - Talal, Marilynn (Box 76)
        - At the Family Table (Box 76)
        - [The caller leaves no message…] (Box 76)
        - Feeding the Fish at Hanauma Bay (Box 76)
        - Gold-Miner Outside Fairbanks (Box 76)
        - How She Went from Yellow to Pink (Box 76)
        - Mornings Before School (Box 76)
        - Mrs. Shapanka's Embrace (Box 76)
        - Mummy in the De Young Museum (Box 76)
        - One-Eyed Hens (Box 76)
        - Outside Fairbanks (Box 76)
        - Self-Portrait from the Fifties (Box 76)
        - Summer Blossoms (Box 76)
        - Through the Iron Hush (Box 76)
        - To Be Continued… (Box 76)
        - The Unbinding of Sarah (Box 76)
      - Tanner, Ron (Box 76)
        - High Heat for Cotton (Box 76)
        - Jackpot (Box 76)
        - The Lesson [aka The Big Picture] (Box 76)
      - Tanner, Tony (Box 76)
        - Review of I Am Elijah Thrush (Box 76)
      - Targan, Barry (Box 76)
        - Kingdoms (Box 76)
      - Tarnoff, Deborah (Box 76)
        - In a Manner of Speaking (Box 76)
      - Taylor. Harry H. (Box 76)
        - Plot Outline of The Man Who Married Before (Box 76)
      - Taylor, Kent (Box 76)
        - Brain Tumor (Box 76)
        - Medical Records (Box 76)
      - Taylor, Jr., E.F. (Box 76)
        - Laughing Sutra (Box 76)
      - Taylor, Leeka (Box 76)
        - The Curtain Rises (Box 76)
      - Tennant, Emma (Box 76)
        - The Boss's Wife (Box 76)
      - Tester, William (Box 76)
        - Darling Draft 1 (Box 76)
        - Darling Draft 2, (3 folders (Box 76)
      - Theroux, Alexander (Box 76)
        - Stories, (6 folders (Box 76)
          - The Copernicus Affair (Box 76)
          - Edward Gorey (Box 76)
          - Evangelist (Box 76)
          - The Faculty Wife (Box 76)
          - Herbert Head, Gent. (Box 76)
          - Lynda van Cats (Box 76)
          - The Master's Oral (Box 76)
          - The Obsolescent Lobster (Box 76)
          - The Psychiatrist (Box 76)
          - The Sissy (Box 76)
          - Southern Manners (Box 76)
          - Theroux Metaphrastes (Box 76)
      - Thibeau, Jack (Box 76)
        - Eat Your Heart Out, Circe [aka I'd Take Circe to the City but She'd Turn Everyone to Pigs ] (Box 76)
      - Thompson, Earl (Box 76)
        - The Header, the Rigger, the Captain (Box 76)
      - Thomas, James (Box 76)
        - Paco and I at Sea (Box 76)
          - Half Frame (Box 76)
          - Sparkle in Five (Box 76)
          - Santorini Gray (Box 76)
          - Last Factory Blues (Box 76)
          - My Journal as the Fishwoman (Box 76)
          - Blood Money (Box 76)
          - Paco and I at Sea (Box 76)
          - Christmas in Calpe (Box 76)
          - Talma Levy Is Falling (Box 76)
          - Barbecue (Box 76)
    - Thornburn - Wehle (Box 77)
      - Thorburn, Russell (Box 77)
        - After Bingo (Box 77)
        - Apollonaire in America (Box 77)
        - Apology to my Father (Box 77)
        - Cocteau Painting a Mural of Angels in a Chapel in Villefranche, Where a Young Boy Holds His Ladder (Box 77)
        - Desire at the Quarry (Box 77)
        - Hotel Memory (Box 77)
        - The Jean Cocteau Fan Club (Box 77)
        - The Judas Fan Club (Box 77)
        - Life on Lesznianska Street (Box 77)
        - Matisse's World Is at a Standstill (Box 77)
        - The Mexican Baseball League (Box 77)
        - Playing Frisbee without My Shirt (Box 77)
        - [What a Dickensian bunch…] (Box 77)
      - Toma, T.L. (Box 77)
        - The Exchange (Box 77)
      - Topp, Mike (Box 77)
        - Erik Satie (Box 77)
        - The Evil Empire (Box 77)
        - Young Peas (Box 77)
      - Trelawny, Victor (Box 77)
        - The Illusions of Youth (Box 77)
        - The Kid with His Mind in the Sewer (Box 77)
        - Murder on the Mass Market (Box 77)
        - On the Job (Box 77)
        - Prestige (Box 77)
        - Sailboard (Box 77)
        - Seventy-Three's Not So Bad (Box 77)
        - The Super Bowl Is Usually Over by Halftime Too (Box 77)
      - Trell, Max (Box 77)
        - The Small Gods and Mr. Barnum (Box 77)
      - Trilling, Lionel (Box 77)
        - [Ever since I first took charge…] (Box 77)
      - Troyan, Sheila (Box 77)
        - The Mountain (Box 77)
      - Trussell, Donna (Box 77)
        - Fishbone (Box 77)
        - On Sky-Vue Boulevard (Box 77)
        - To Miss Candance Amyes, Lost on the Titanic (Box 77)
      - Tuck, Lilly (Box 77)
        - Stories (Box 77)
          - Dog (Box 77)
          - Impotence (Box 77)
          - Yesterday, Today, Tomorrow (Box 77)
        - Interviewing Matisse or The Woman Who Died Standing Up, (2 folders) (Box 77)
      - Turner, Gregory (Box 77)
        - Thank you, Egypt (Box 77)
      - Ullian, Robert (Box 77)
        - A Snag in the Warp (Box 77)
      - Unger, Donald N. (Box 77)
        - Peaks and Valleys (Box 77)
        - Public Works (Box 77)
      - Ungerer, Kathryn, (2 folders) (Box 77)
        - Stories, (2 folders) (Box 77)
          - The Conception of Angels (Box 77)
          - Eternity (Box 77)
          - Harmony (Box 77)
          - How I Saw the Bears Dancing North of Nain (Box 77)
          - La Marquesa in Solitary (Box 77)
          - Red Dress, Yello Dress: Chronicles and Indulgences (Box 77)
          - Weed and Bone (Box 77)
      - Unrue, Jane Elizabeth (Box 77)
        - The Chair (Box 77)
        - Eating from the Box (Box 77)
        - It Is Too Old (Box 77)
        - Killers (Box 77)
        - Man and Duck and Cracker and the Phylogenetic Question (Box 77)
        - Production (Box 77)
        - (Untitled) (Box 77)
      - Updike, John (Box 77)
        - The Bankrupt Man (Box 77)
        - Protect Us and Keep Us, Mrs. O. (Box 77)
      - Van de Graaff, Leonard (Box 77)
        - On a Painting by Edward Hopper (Box 77)
      - VanArsdall, R. (Box 77)
        - The Spirits Will Win Through: An Interview with Barry Hannah (Box 77)
      - Vannatta, Dennis (Box 77)
        - Thetis, Mary, and Mother (Box 77)
      - Vaughan, Samuel S. (Box 77)
        - Medium Rare: A Look at the Book and Its People (Box 77)
      - Viegener, Matias (Box 77)
        - The Black Prince (Box 77)
      - Vinz, Mark (Box 77)
        - Art Isn't Long Enough [aka The Lost Story Man] (Box 77)
      - Vogrin, Valerie (Box 77)
        - Unborrowing the Sugar (Box 77)
      - Vreuls, Diane (Box 77)
        - Are We There Yet? (3 folders) (Box 77)
      - Vukcevich, Ray (Box 77)
        - In the Refrigerator (Box 77)
      - Vukelich, George (Box 77)
        - The Bosun's Chair (Box 77)
      - Waddington, Chris (Box 77)
        - A Story from When I Was a Boy [aka Like Glue] (Box 77)
      - Walker, John (Box 77)
        - Untitled Collection (Box 77)